Guide to the Serpent's Tail/High Risk Archives ca. 1990-1997 MSS 86 MSS 086
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Production files
  - Klein, Adam--version of text, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Klein, Adam--misc, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Lewis, Heather, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - McCoy, Horace, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Meer, Ameena--version of the text, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Meer, Ameena--version of the text, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Meer, Ameena--misc, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Meer, Ameena--printing, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Meer, Ameena--typesetting, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Mueller, Cookie--manuscript, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Page specs (Ted), undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Postcards, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Purdy, James, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Reprints, 1994; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Reprints, 1994; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Reprints--first season, general correspondence, undated; 31142040617139 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Reprints--Guibert, Herve, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Reprints--Indiana, Gary, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Reprints--Jordan, June, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Reprints--Kennedy, Pagan, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Reprints--Meer, Ameena, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Reprints--Sapphire, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Reprints--seller / shipper 1994, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Reprints--Weiss, Daniel Evan, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Reprints--Weissman, Benjamin, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Rower, Ann, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Sales catalogue, fall 1995 / winter 1996 & galleys, 1995-1996; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Sales catalogue, fall 1995 / winter 1996 & galleys, 1995-1996; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Smith, Jack, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Thumbnail blanks, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Tillman, Lynne, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Trinidad, David--manuscript, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Trinidad, David--version of text, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Trinidad, David--version of text, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Trinidad, David--misc, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Trinidad, David--printing, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Valenzuela, Luisa--misc, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Valenzuela, Luisa--printing, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Weiss, Daniel Evan--copy, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Weiss, Daniel Evan--misc, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Weiss, Daniel Evan--printing, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Weiss, Daniel Evan--typesetting, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Weissman, Benjamin--copy, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Weissman, Benjamin--misc, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Weissman, Benjamin--printing, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Weissman, Benjamin--typesetting, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Wurlitzer, Rudolph, undated; 31142040617147 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Series V: Publicity, photographs and sales catalogs
  - Subseries A: Publicity and promotion
    - Advertising, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bookmarks, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Cover flats, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Cover flats, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cover flats, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Cover flats, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Cover flats, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Cover flats, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Cover flats (see flat box), undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 8a)
    - Covers, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Covers, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - FAB Award (Firecracker Alternative Book Awards), undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Postcards, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Press--general HR, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Press--Rex Ray, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Press--general ST, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Press--general ST, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Press--Midnight Classics, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Press binder--Abella, Alex, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Press binder--Acker, Kathy, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Press binder--Agard, John, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Press binder--Albert, Susan Wittig, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Press binder--Altman, Dennis, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Press binder--Amado, Jorge, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Press binder--Andreacchi, Grace, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Press binder--Ayrton, Pete, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Press binder--Banti, Anna, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Press binder--Baratham, Gopal, A Candle or the Sun, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Press binder--Baratham, Gopal, Moonrise, Sunset, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Press binder--Barrett, Keverne, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Press binder--Bartlett, Neil, Who Was That Man?, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Press binder--Bartlett, Neil, Mr. Clive and Mr. Page, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Press binder--Belben, Rosalind, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Press binder--Biermann, Pieke, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Press binder--Blincoe, Nick, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Press binder--Bornstein / Sullivan, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Press binder--Breakwell / Hammond, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Press binder--Brotchie, Alastair, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Press binder--Bruen, Ken, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Press binder--B, Alexandra, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Press binder--Burroughs, William, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Press binder--Bush, Catherine, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Press binder--Caesar, Ann & Michael, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Press binder--Caistor, Nick, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Press binder--Campbell, Alison, et al, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Press binder--Camus, Renaud, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Press binder--Cannon, Michael, The Borough, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Press binder--Cannon, Michael, Conspiracy of Hope, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Press binder--Carter / Watney, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Press binder--Cavazzoni, Ermanno, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Press binder--Caveney / Young, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Press binder--Celati, Gianni, Appearances, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Press binder--Celati, Gianni, Voices from the Plain, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Press binder--Charef, Mehdi, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Press binder--Charyn, Jerome, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Press binder--Chedid, Andr/unittitle>, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Press binder--Chirbes, Rafael, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Press binder--Chomsky, Noam, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Press binder--Coe, Sue, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Press binder--Cooper, Dennis, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Press binder--Cooper, Fiona, I Believe in Angels, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Press binder--Cooper, Fiona, Jay Loves Lucy, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Press binder--Cooper, Fiona, Skyhook in the Midnight Sun, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Press binder--Cooper, Fiona, Blossom at the Mention, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Press binder--Cortez, Jayne, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Press binder--County, Jayne, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Press binder--Coyne, Kevin, The Party Dress, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Press binder--Coyne, Kevin, Show Business, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Press binder--Czerniawski, Adam, undated; 31142040617154 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Press binder--Daeninckx, Didier--A Very Profitable War, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Press binder--Daeninckx, Didier--Murder In Memoriam, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Press binder--Dale, John, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Press binder--Davis, Lydia, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Press binder--De Chirico, Giorgio, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Press binder--DeLynn, Jane, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Press binder--De Souza, Daniel, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Press binder--Dlugos, Tim, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Press binder--Dowell, Coleman, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Press binder--Duffy, Maureen, et. al, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Press binder--Duffy, Stella, Calendar Girl, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Press binder--Duffy, Stella, Wavewalker, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Press binder--Duncker, Patricia, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Press binder--Dunn, Suzannah, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Press binder--Durlacher, Gerhard--Drowning, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Press binder--Durlacher, Gerhard, Stripes in the Sky, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Press binder--Ehrenburg, Ilya, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Press binder--Eltit, Diamela, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Press binder--Etchart, Julio, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Press binder--Fakinou, Eugenia, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Press binder--Fell, Alison, Seven Cardinal Virtues, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Press binder--Fell, Alison, Seven Deadly Sins, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Press binder--Fell, Alison, Mer de Glace, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Press binder--Fell, Alison, Pillow Boy of the Lady Onogoro, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Press binder--Fell, Alison, Serious Hysterics, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Press binder--Fichte, Hubert, Detlev's Imitations, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Press binder--Fichte, Hubert, The Orphanage, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Press binder--Figes, Kate, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Press binder--Fried, Erich, Children and Fools, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Press binder--Galas, Diamanda, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Press binder--Gale / King / Wakefield, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Press binder--Gardiner, James, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Press binder--Gerrard / McCarthy, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Press binder--Gilroy, Paul, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Press binder--Giorno, John, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Press binder--Glantz, Margo, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Press binder--Glück, Robert, Elements of a Coffee Service, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Press binder--Glück, Robert, Jack the Modernist, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Press binder--Glück, Robert, Margery Kempe, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Press binder--Glück, Robert, Reader, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Press binder--Gordon, Graeme, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Press binder--Goytisolo, Juan, Marks of Identity, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Press binder--Goytisolo, Juan, Juan the Landless, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Press binder--Goytisolo, Juan, Virtues of the Solitary Bird, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Press binder--Goytisolo, Juan, Makbara, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Press binder--Graham, Barry, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Press binder--Greer, Bonnie, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Press binder--Guibert, Herve. The Gangsters, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Press binder--Guibert, Herve. My Parents, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Press binder--Guibert, Herve. To the Friend Who Did Not, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Press binder--Hall, Albyn Leah, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Press binder--Haut, Woody, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Press binder--Hayward / Lefanu, The God, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Press binder--Hayward / Lefanu, Obsession, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Press binder--Haywood, Gar Anthony, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Press binder--Hochschild, Adam, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Press binder--Home, Stewart, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Press binder--Hopkinson, Amanda, Desires & Disguises, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Press binder--Hopkinson, Amanda, Forbidden Rainbow, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Press binder--Hoskyns, Barney, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Press binder--Hoyland, John, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Press binder--Humann, Klaus, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Press binder--Indiana, Gary, Let It Bleed, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Press binder--Indiana, Gary, Gone Tomorrow, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Press binder--Indiana, Gary, Rent Boy, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Press binder--Jakubowski, Maxim, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Press binder--James, C.L.R., undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Press binder--Jelinek, Elfriede, Lust, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Press binder--Jelinek, Elfriede, The Piano Teacher, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Press binder--Jelinek, Elfriede, Wonderful Wonderful Time, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Press binder--Jelinek, Elfriede, Women as Lovers, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Press binder--Jordan, June, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Press binder--Kennedy, Pagan, Spinsters, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Press binder--Kennedy, Pagan, Stripping, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Press binder--Kharms, Daniil, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Press binder--Klein, Adam, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Press binder--Knopf, Mary, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Press binder--Kordi, Gohar, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Press binder--LAB (London Arts Board), undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Press binder--Lambert, Gavin, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Press binder--Langford, Diane, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Press binder--Lansbury, James, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Press binder--Leon, Stephen, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Press binder--Lewis, Heather, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Press binder--Liksom, Rosa, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Press binder--Loader, James, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Press binder--Maraini, Dacia, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Press binder--Mark, M, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Press binder--Marshall, Paule, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Press binder--Masoliver, Juan Antonio, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Press binder--McCoy, Horace, I Should Have Stayed Home, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Press binder--McCoy, Horace, Kill Tomorrow Good-bye, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Press binder--McCoy, Horace, They Shoot Horses Don't They?, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Press binder--Meer, Ameena, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Press binder--Meyers, Stewart, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - Press binder--Mildmay, Eroica, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - Press binder--Modjeska, Drusilla, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - Press binder--Moncur, Susan, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - Press binder--Moore, Olive, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - Press binder--Moore, Suzanne, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - Press binder--Mosley, Walter, Black Betty, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - Press binder--Mosley, Walter, A Red Death, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - Press binder--Mosley, Walter, White Butterfly, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - Press binder--Mosley, Walter, RL's Dream, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 172)
    - Press binder--Moyano, Daniel, The Devil's Trill, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 173)
    - Press binder--Moyano, Daniel, Flight of the Tiger, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - Press binder--M Herta, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - Press binder--Nayman, Mich, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - Press binder--Neale, Jonathan, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - Press binder--Nuñez Raul, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - Press binder--Oe, Kenzaburo, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 179)
    - Press binder--Olson, Jenni, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - Press binder--Onetti, Juan Carlos, The Shipyard, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 181)
    - Press binder--Onetti, Juan Carlos, A Brief Life, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 182)
    - Press binder--Palandri, Enrico, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - Press binder--Peake, Tony, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 184)
    - Press binder--Pelecanos, George P, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 185)
    - Press binder--Pessoa, Fernando, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 186)
    - Press binder--Printer's Devil, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 187)
    - Press binder--Pullinger, Kate, Where Does Kissing End?, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 188)
    - Press binder--Pullinger, Kate, Border Lines, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 189)
    - Press binder--Purdy, James, undated; 31142040617162 (Box 2, Folder 190)
    - Press binder--Rathbone, Julian, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - Press binder--Reaves, Sam, A Long, Cold Fall, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - Press binder--Reaves, Sam, Fear Will Do It, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - Press binder--Reynolds, Simon, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - Press binder--Reynolds / Press, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - Press binder--Rogers, James, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - Press binder--Rose, Cynthia, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - Press binder--Rose / Texier, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - Press binder--Rowe, Marsha, Sex and the City, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - Press binder--Rowe, Marsha, Sacred Space, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - Press binder--Rowe, Marsha, So Very English, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - Press binder--Rower, Ann, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - Press binder--R Juan, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - Press binder--Russell, Mary, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - Press binder--Saer, Juan Jose--The Witness, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - Press binder--Saer, Juan Jose--The Event, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - Press binder--Saer, Juan Jose--Nobody Nothing Never, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - Press binder--Sander, Helke, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - Press binder--Sanza, Silvia, Twice Real, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Press binder--Sanza, Silvia, Alex Wants To Call It Love, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Press binder--Sapphire, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Press binder--Satie, Erik, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Press binder--Schmidt, Susan, Out of America, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Press binder--Schmidt, Susan, Winging It, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 214)
    - Press binder--Scott, Mary, Not in Newbury, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - Press binder--Scott, Mary, Nudists May Be Encountered, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - Press binder--Segrave, Elisa, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - Press binder--Serpent's Tail (general), undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - Press binder--Smoke Signals, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - Press binder--Srivastava, Atima, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - Press binder--Tillman, Lynne, Absence Makes the Heart, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - Press binder--Tillman, Lynne, Cast In Doubt, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 222)
    - Press binder--Tillman, Lynne, Haunted Houses, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 223)
    - Press binder--Tillman, Lynne, Motion Sickness, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - Press binder--Tondelli, Pier Vittorio, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 225)
    - Press binder--Toop, David, Ocean of Sound, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 226)
    - Press binder--Toop, David, Rap Attack 2, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 227)
    - Press binder--Tremblay, Michel, The Fat Woman Next, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 228)
    - Press binder--Tremblay, Michel, Making Room, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - Press binder--Trinidad, David, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 230)
    - Press binder--Valenzuela, Luisa, Bedside Manners, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 231)
    - Press binder--Valenzuela, Luisa, The Lizard's Tail, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - Press binder--Valenzuela, Luisa, Open Door, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 233)
    - Press binder--Vazquez Montalban, Manuel, Angst-Ridden Executive, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 234)
    - Press binder--Vazquez Montalban, Manuel, Olympic Death, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 235)